<email>
    <subject>Important: Submit Your Voter Form to Your Election Office</subject>
    <from>US Vote Helpdesk &lt;voterhelpdesk@usvotefoundation.org&gt;</from>
   <reply_to>voterhelpdesk@usvotefoundation.org</reply_to>
    <body_template><![CDATA[
<div style="font-family: 'Trebuchet MS', Arial, sans-serif;">
	<p><strong>Dear $!firstName,</strong></p>
	<p>One step left! You must submit your signed Registration / Absentee Ballot Request form to your election office. Print, sign and send to the address provided in the instructions, or look up the address in the <a href="https://www.usvotefoundation.org/vote/eoddomestic.htm">Election Official Directory</a></p>

	<p>You can check your <a href="https://www.usvotefoundation.org/vote/sviddomestic.htm">State Requirements/ Voter Materials Transmission Options</a> to see the various options for returning your form. </p>


<p>Your signature is part of your voter identity, so keep your signature consistent on all voting materials. </p>

<p>If you can't print your form now, here is a link so you can print later: <a href="https://$!url/DownloadLinkPage.htm?generationUUID=$!id">Click to Download Form</a> <br/>
This link is valid for 7 days.</p>


  <p><strong><a href="https://www.usvotefoundation.org/voter-reward-badge">Get your Voter Reward Badge!</strong></a><br/>
Choose your favorite Voter Reward Badge to share on social media. Spread the word to other voters!  Go here to get your badge: <a href="https://www.usvotefoundation.org/voter-reward-badge">https://www.usvotefoundation.org/voter-reward-badge</a>
</p>


<p><strong>Wishing you a great voting experience this year & thank you!</strong> <br/>
 <em>- The team at U.S. Vote Foundation</em></p>

<p><strong>P.S.</strong>  Help us to help other voters. Your contribution makes a difference!</p>

<p>As a nonpartisan, not-for-profit, civic organization, we rely on donations from engaged citizens like you. Please donate now and consider making a recurring donation – a small monthly donation sustains our operations and changes everything about what we can do for you and other voters. <a href="https://www.usvotefoundation.org/donate">www.usvotefoundation.org/donate</a>  </p>

</div>
    ]]></body_template>
</email>
