<email>
    <subject>Important: Submit Your Voter Form to Your Election Office</subject>
    <from>US Vote Helpdesk &lt;voterhelpdesk@usvotefoundation.org&gt;</from>
   <reply_to>voterhelpdesk@usvotefoundation.org</reply_to>
    <body_template><![CDATA[
		<style type="text/css">
			p { font-family: 'Trebuchet MS', Arial, sans-serif; }
			strong { font-weight: bold; }
			a { color: #c00; }

			.comments { color: #888; font-size: smaller; }
		</style>
		<div>
    <p>
	    <a href="https://vote.theskimm.com"><img src="https://usvotefoundation-drupal.s3.amazonaws.com/prod/s3fs-public/theskimm_email_banner.png" alt="SKIMM 2020"/></a>
		<hr style="width: auto; max-width: 700px;margin: 0 auto 0 0;"/>
	</p>
		    <p><strong>Dear $!firstName,</strong></p>

			<p>We're glad you've been able to use the Vote-Print-Mail system to generate your Federal Write-in Absentee Ballot (FWAB) and that you can cast your vote in this important election! Please read the instruction letter carefully.</p>

			<p>You must download, print, sign and send in your FWAB. You can check your <a href="https://www.usvotefoundation.org/vote/sviddomestic.htm">State Requirements/ Voter Materials Transmission Options</a> to confirm the various options for transmitting your form.</p>

			<p><strong>Remember to check the witness requirements and then sign your cover page form</strong> and send it with your ballot to your election official who needs your original signature.</p>
			<p>If the ballot from your election office arrives after you have sent in your FWAB, please complete it and send it in to replace the FWAB.</p>

			<p>US Vote is a nonprofit,  nonpartisan public charity powered by a dedicated team of volunteers. Please help us - <a href="https://www.usvotefoundation.org/donate">Make a Donation Today!</a></p>

			<p>Here's to you for casting your ballot!<br/>
			<em>- From the volunteer team at U.S. Vote Foundation</em></p>


      <p><strong>P.S.  <a href="https://www.usvotefoundation.org/voter-reward-badge">Get your Voter Reward Badge!</strong></a></p>
      <p>Choose from a selection of Voter Reward Badges - spiff up your social media profile and spread the word to other voters!  Go here to get your badge: <a href="https://www.usvotefoundation.org/voter-reward-badge">https://www.usvotefoundation.org/voter-reward-badge</a></p>
      <p><strong>P.P.S. <a href="https://www.usvotefoundation.org/donate">Please give back</a> to Help Us to Help More Voters:</strong></p>
      <p>We work hard to make sure that you can vote. And when you give to us, you can be sure – Every Dollar Counts. And your voting effort goes further.</p>
      <p>$1 x 1 helps assure another voter gets their ballot.</p>
      <p>$1/month has 12 times the impact.</p>
      <p>$3/month has 36 times the impact.</p>
      <p>$10/month has 120 times the impact every year!</p>
      <p><strong>Please Join Us as a Foundation Member - a small monthly contribution will make a major difference – it will change everything about what we can do for you and other voters. Go to <a href="https://www.usvotefoundation.org/donate">https://www.usvotefoundation.org/donate</a></p>

			<p style="font-size:smaller;color:gray; font-family: 'Trebuchet MS', Arial, sans-serif;">Contact us at <a href="mailto:voterhelpdesk@usvotefoundation.org">voterhelpdesk@usvotefoundation.org</a> anytime with questions or comments.<br />

			&copy;2005-$!year Overseas Vote. All Rights Reserved.</p>
		</div>
    ]]></body_template>
</email>
